markable.in 2017-03-18

# Markable.in

This privacy policy sets out how Markable uses and protects any information that you give Markable when you use this application.

Markable is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this application, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

This policy is effective from 05/01/2012.

### 1\. What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * (optional) contact information including email address
  * (optional) system version of your iOS device

### 2\. What we do with the information we gather

We gather this information to understand your needs, improve our products and provide you with a better service.

### 3\. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### 4\. Links to other websites

Our application may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our application, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### 5\. Controlling your personal information

You may choose to not signing up a Markable account in order to prevent the collection or use of your personal information. Markable is committed to respect your privacy by making the most functionality available should you choose to not sign up.

If you have signed up for an account with us through the application, you can access or change your personally information by logging into your account and editing your profile.

We may retain original and updated information for reasons such as technical constraints, dispute resolution, troubleshooting, record retention, and enforcement of our agreements. For security purposes, we may request information to help verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your information.

### 6\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at this email address [support@markable.in](mailto:support@markable.in).
